Please! Wait, ma'am!
- Don't fire me immediately!
- Throw her to the ground!
[GROANS, PANTING] Ma'am!
Where's the due process, ma'am?
Shut up!
Go to the Supreme Court
if you want due process!
You dare claim
that you're the inheritor
of this hotel?
- Ma'am!
- [SCREAMING HYSTERICALLY]
[SCREAMING] The audacity!
[GRUNTS]
[SOBBING, SNIFFLING]
Where did it go?
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Mom...
[SOBBING, SNIFFLING CONTINUES]
How could they be
so cruel to me?
[CAR DOOR OPENS]
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
What happened?
You! Why did you have
to come into my life?!
I lost my job!
I never should have left you
alone with them.
No! You're bad luck!
Go back to your girlfriend!
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
She's not my...
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Your necklace.
My father gave it to my mother
as a gift.
I'll return it as soon as I can.
Huh?
[THUDS]
That's mine!
- [DOOR CLOSES]
- Hey!
It's mine!
Hey!
She's not your mother!
Mother stealer!
[SIGHS]
[SOBBING, SNIFFLING]
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]